Reader: The girl looked out the window dreamily.
Vivienne: ÔMr Hartley,Ő
Reader: she said slowly,
Vivienne: ÔI donŐt know what to say to you.
I understand all the advantages of your offer,
and sometimes I feel sure that I could be happy with you.
But, then sometimes I am less sure.
I was born a city girl,
and I am not sure that I would enjoy living a quiet life in the suburbs.Ő
Hartley: ÔMy dear girl,Ő
Reader: said Hartley,
Hartley: ÔYou will have everything that you want.
You can come to the city for the theatre,
for shopping, and to visit your friends as often as you want.
You can trust me, canŐt you?Ő
Vivienne: ÔI can trust you completely,Ő
Reader: she said, smiling at him.
Vivienne: ÔI know you are the kindest of men,
and that the girl who you get will be very lucky.
I heard all about you when I was at the MontgomerysŐ.Ő
Hartley: ÔAh!Ő
Reader: exclaimed Hartley,
Hartley: ÔI remember so well the evening I first saw you at the MontgomerysŐ.
I will never forget that dinner.
Come on, Vivienne, promise me.
I want you.
Nobody else will ever give you such a happy home.Ő
Reader: Vivienne didnŐt answer.
Suddenly Hartley was suspicious.
Hartley: ÔTell me, Vivienne, is thereÉŐ
Reader: he asked,
Hartley: ÔÉis there someone else?Ő
Vivienne: ÔYou shouldn't ask that, Mr. Hartley,Ő
Reader: she said.
Vivienne: ÔBut I will tell you.
There is one other personÉbut I havenŐt promised him anything.Ő
Hartley: ÔVivienne,Ő
Reader: said Hartley masterfully.
Hartley: ÔYou must be mine.Ő
Reader: Vivienne looked him in the eye.
Vivienne: ÔDo you think for one moment,Ő
Reader: she said calmly,
Vivienne: Ôthat I could come to your home while HŽloise is there?Ő